From the schedule and assessment setting
page, go to the assessment settings tab.
cue-2
Here, you will see a list of scored
activities. You can manage them one by one
cue-3
or in bulk.
cue-4
Let's look at settings for individual
assessments first.
cue-5
Each activity includes multiple settings
you can adjust regarding when and how
cue-6
students experience it. To do so, simply
click and select or enter your changes.
cue-7
To mention a few tips, the time of date
here follows the 24-hour system.
cue-8
Enabling targeted retake mode will allow
students to only redo questions they got
cue-9
wrong. Also, passwords and exceptions will
help set special access rules or
cue-10
accommodations for individual students.
You can also use the search bar to search
cue-11
for specific assessment names. Now, let's
look into the bulk apply function. With
cue-12
many assessments, managing one by one can
be tedious. Bulk apply allows you to copy
cue-13
settings for one assessment and apply them
to all the others, except for the
cue-14
available date and due date. For example,
here I changed the number of attempts and
cue-15
late policy of the Getting Started
assessment. All I need to do is to select
cue-16
it from the list, click bulk apply, and
confirm. This applies your
cue-17
selected setting to all assessment at
once. Really time-saving, right? There
cue-18
will be another video explaining student
progress and insights. If you have
cue-19
additional questions, visit our OLI help
page.